tushyraw.com 2019-04-27

# Privacy Policy : TUSHYRAW.com

Last updated: 29 March 2018

This Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect, use, and share your information. It also describes your rights regarding the data we store. Please read this document carefully.

But before we get started, here is an...

### Important notice regarding adult content

This is an **adult website** that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents on this website. If you are under the age of 18 and/or under the age of majority in the jurisdiction you reside and from which you access the website, you must leave this site immediately, and your account can be terminated without notice.

### Who we are

This website is operated by General Media Systems, LLC and is part of the VIXEN network of websites that includes blacked.com, blackedraw.com, vixen.com and tushy.com, as well as other websites.

You can contact us by email [support@tushyraw.com](mailto:support@tushyraw.com)

### Disclaimer

By using this website, you agree that we may use any personal information you have provided or that has been collected for any purpose within the constraints of the law, including technical, administrative, research and development, customer administration, marketing, trading of personal data, age verification, promotion and advertising by this website or authorized third parties.

By using this site, you agree that the site may, within the constraints of the law, share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information that it has gathered or collected with third parties.

All information collected may be shared to comply with applicable law and / or to cooperate with law enforcement agencies and courts/tribunals.

### What data we collect and why

In order to **provide our service** when you subscribe we collect the following data from you:

\- Your **email address** , **username** and **password** so you can log in to the website and we can provide you with information about your account.  
\- Your **IP address** to determine your general location and protect your account from being hacked.  
\- Your **name** , **country** , **ZIP** or **post code** , **credit card** or **other billing information** , through a third party billing provider (as listed below), so we can charge you the subscription fees.

We also occasionally send you **content updates** and **special offers** from us or our partners. You can opt out of receiving these at any time in your [Account Settings](https://members.tushyraw.com/account).

### Keeping your data secure

All of your data is stored securely.

We have adopted and implemented industry standard technology for maintaining the security of all personal information collected by our websites.

While we use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to secure your personal information, the transmission of information via the Internet can never be one hundred percent secure. As a result, we can assume no liability if information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

### Who we share your data with (and why)

We only ever share your personal data with other companies if necessary for the operation of our websites. These other companies are legally required to have the same data security standards we do. Below you can find a complete list of who we might share your data with. Note that we may change our partners in the future, in which case this document will be updated.

Why| What| Who  
---|---|---  
  
Billing

| 

Credit card, email, first and last name, country, ZIP or post code

| 

If you sign up to one or more of our websites, your credit card or other billing data is processed by one of our payment processors; [EPOCH](https://epoch.com/billingsupport), [SEGPAY](http://cs.segpay.com/), VXNBILL, [CCBILL](https://support.ccbill.com/), [CENTROBILL](https://centrobill.com/consumer/contact.html) or [ECHST](https://www.echst.net/), .

You can tell which of these companies processes your data from both the page you see when you pay for your subscription, as well as from the billing related emails you receive.

We also store billing related data (email, first and last name, country, but not your credit card or other payment information) in our internal systems.  
  
Support

| 

Email, and sometimes more

| 

In order to help you with any support requests our customer support team uses tools hosted by [Zendesk](https://www.zendesk.com/). We only store your email address in Zendesk if you contact us. In some cases, in order to provide you with the support you require, other data you provide might be stored with Zendesk over the course of your support request. In addition sometimes information needs to be shared with our technical teams so we can investigate or action your requests.  
  
Marketing

| 

Email address

| 

We use [Sparkpost](https://www.sparkpost.com/) to process our email campaigns, and we will share your email address with them to send you the emails you requested.  
  
Hosting & Security

| 

All data

| 

We use [Amazon Web Services](https://aws.amazon.com/) to host our websites on its infrastructure in the USA. We also use Amazon Web Services to host all data (including yours) in securely encrypted form. On top of that we use [Loggly](https://www.loggly.com/) and [Cloudflare](https://www.cloudflare.com/) to protect both ourselves and you from fraudulent attempts to access the site and your data.  
  
### How long we store your data

Unless you ask to have it deleted, we will store your data indefinitely in order to give you continued access to any content that was present at the time your subscription ended.

### Advertising and Offers

If you click on any advertising or special offers on this website you may be directed to a third party website that is outside our control, and in some cases, we might share some data with those websites in order to make things easier for you. In these cases, you are responsible for making sure that these websites keep your data as safe as we do.

### Cookies

Like almost every other website, we use cookies (small bits of data stored on your device) to enable, secure and improve the operation of our websites.

These cookies don’t contain any personally identifiable data, and they are used for various purposes like tracking your movement through the sites in order to help us to improve your experience, serving you relevant advertising, making sure that we can pay affiliates, keeping you logged in between visits, etc.

Every browser offers the option to delete or block these cookies, usually in their settings options.

### Special provisions for users covered by the GDPR

Please note that, as stated above, your data will be stored on our partners’ servers in the USA.

### Which countries are covered by the GDPR

We apply GDPR guidelines for all users in the EU, EEA, the microstates of Andorra, Monaco and San Marino, as well as Switzerland.

### Your data rights

You have the right to **access** or **rectify** the personally identifiable data we hold about you.

You also have the right to ask for your data to be **deleted**. Just keep in mind that we might need it in order to fulfil the rest of your subscription.

If you want to access, rectify or delete your data, please send us an [email](mailto:support@tushyraw.com).

### Optional Features

We ask **consent** from you to share your data with partners at certain times, as well as to use your email address to send you **content updates** and **special offers** from us or our partners. If you do not give us consent to do so we will not share your data and you will not receive these emails. You can change your email marketing setting at any time in your [Account Settings](https://members.tushyraw.com/account).

### Complaints

In the unfortunate case where you are not happy with our privacy policy or processes, and where we can’t resolve the issue together, you have the right to file a complaint with a supervisory authority. This can be the supervisory authority of your country if you’re in the EU/EEA, or otherwise the [Maltese Data Protection Authority](https://idpc.org.mt/).
